Guide to the Abraham Aronow Photographs
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- San Francisco Community Photographs, circa 1981-2009; Series II; 1.25; (7 boxes)
  - Photographic Prints 8 by 10 Inches
    - Qual-Med, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1992 December 16 (Box 12, Folder 307)
    - Rolling In Repose, Muni, N-Judah, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 308-309)
    - Seat of Culture, Palace of the Legion of Honor, San Francisco, California, 2004 July 14 (Box 12, Folder 310)
    - Side by Side, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 311)
    - Sidewalk Café, 18th Street near Castro, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 312)
    - Site for Sore Eyes, undated (Box 12, Folder 313)
    - Smokin', San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 314)
      Street portrait with a Sabattier effect
    - Snooze and Shadow, undated (Box 12, Folder 315)
    - Sonata for Sun and Strings, The Cannery, San Francisco, California, 1992 December 25 (Box 12, Folder 316)
    - Special Friends, Castro, San Francisco, California, undated; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 12, Folder 317-318)
    - Street Portrait, West Portal, San Francisco, California, 1998 August 6 (Box 12, Folder 319)
    - Stuffed Window, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 320)
    - The Sun Is Past the Yardarm, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 12, Folder 321)
    - Sun Warrior, Street Fair, Castro, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 322)
    - Supine, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 323)
    - Time Outside, General Store, Stage Road, San Gregorio, California, 2008 January 16 (Box 12, Folder 324)
    - Tonality in Photography, Pescadero, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 325)
    - Un Real Leather, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 326)
    - Unlawful Sex, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 327)
    - Voyages Unlimited, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 328)
    - Wigs, Oakland, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 329)
    - Window Display, Geary Boulevard, San Francisco, California, 2004 July 14 (Box 12, Folder 330)
    - Woe, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 12, Folder 331)
    - Worn Out in the West, Castro, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 12, Folder 332)
    - Young Man, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 12, Folder 333)
  - Photographic Prints 11 x 14 Inches, undated
    - Angel of Love, Haight Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 13, Folder 334)
    - Apres Surf, Ocean Beach, San Francisco, California, undated; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 13, Folder 335-336)
    - Askance, Sullivan Reception at the Art Institute, San Francisco, California, 2003, June 14 (Box 13, Folder 337)
    - B & R in the Castro, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 13, Folder 338)
    - Bad Boys, San Francisco, California, 2003 July 23 (Box 13, Folder 339)
    - Bags and Bundle, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 13, Folder 340)
    - Behind the Flag, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 13, Folder 341)
    - Best Foot Forward, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 18 (Box 13, Folder 342)
    - Betty and Body, Alameda Flea Market, Alameda, California, 2009 June 7 (Box 13, Folder 343)
    - Beyond Your Wildest Dreams!, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 13, Folder 344)
    - Billboard, Castro Street, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 13, Folder 345)
    - Blind Street Musician, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 13, Folder 346)
    - Bridge Watcher, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 13, Folder 347)
    - Busst and Genes, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 13, Folder 348)
    - Castro Couple, Halloween, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 13, Folder 349)
    - A Chat in the Sun, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 13, Folder 350)
    - Christmas Wish, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 13, Folder 351)
    - Cleavage and Barbed Wire, Union Square, San Francisco, California, 2009 March 31 (Box 13, Folder 352)
    - Closely Cropped Couple, Pescadero, California, circa 1981 (Box 13, Folder 353)
    - A Cluster of Gentlemen, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 13, Folder 354)
    - Coffin Corner, San Gregorio General Store, San Gregorio, California, 2008 January 16 (Box 13, Folder 355)
    - Community Rentals, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 13, Folder 356)
    - Corrugated Cross, Folsom and Erie Streets, San Francisco, California, 2004 November 24 (Box 13, Folder 357)
    - Courtyard, Clarendon Ave, San Francisco, California, undated; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 14, Folder 358-359)
    - Coven, Duboce Park, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 14, Folder 360)
    - Crunch and Astound, Muni Station, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 14, Folder 361)
    - Donna at the Tennessee Grill, Taraval Street, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 14, Folder 362)
    - Double Rainbow, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 14, Folder 363)
    - Elvira, San Francisco, California, 2005 March (Box 14, Folder 364)
    - Entangled in the News, Castro and Market, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 14, Folder 365)
    - Entry, San Francisco MOMA, San Francisco, California, 2000 December 22 (Box 14, Folder 366)
    - Expose Yourself to Knowledge, Oakland, California, undated (Box 14, Folder 367)
    - Fashion, Night Window, near Union Square, San Francisco, California, 2009 March 31 (Box 14, Folder 368)
    - Father and Son, Counter Point, Palace of the Legion of Honor, San Francisco, California, 2004 July 14 (Box 14, Folder 369)
    - First Bite, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 14, Folder 370)
    - First Drink in a Bar, North Beach, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 14, Folder 371)
    - For Auld Lange's Sign, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 14, Folder 372)
    - Fort Point, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 14, Folder 373)
    - French Sailors, San Francisco, California, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 374)
    - Gang of Four, Duboce Park, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 14, Folder 375)
    - Gentlemen All, De Young Museum, San Francisco, California, 2006 January 24 (Box 14, Folder 376)
    - Gentlemen in Waiting, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 14, Folder 377)
    - Gentlemen of Castro, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 14, Folder 378)
    - Gesture, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 14, Folder 379)
    - Girl With Doll, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 14, Folder 380)
    - A Good Read, Castro and Market, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 14, Folder 381)
    - Great Expectations, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 14, Folder 382)
    - The Grope, Folsom Street, San Francisco, California, 2003 December 24 (Box 15, Folder 383)
    - Hanging Out, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 15, Folder 384)
    - Happy Patrons, Tennessee Grill, Taraval Street, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 15, Folder 385)
    - Heads Up, Alameda Flea Market, Alameda, California, 2009 June 7 (Box 15, Folder 386)
    - Homage to Kertész, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 15, Folder 387)
    - Hot Grill, Castro, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 15, Folder 388)
    - Intersecting Planes, De Young Museum, San Francisco, California, 2006 January 24 (Box 15, Folder 389)
    - Jesus is the Reason for the Season, San Francisco, California, 1987; 1 photographic print, 8 x 10 inches in a mat, 11 x 14 inches, signed by Aronow (Box 15, Folder 390)
    - Keys of Accord, Alameda Flea Market, Alameda, California, 2009 June 7 (Box 15, Folder 391)
    - Lacey, Shirley. Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 15, Folder 392)
    - The Ladies' Auxiliary, Haight Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 15, Folder 393)
    - Lady in Black, Noe Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 15, Folder 394)
    - Laid Back in Alameda, Alameda Flea Market, Alameda, California, 2009 June 7 (Box 15, Folder 395)
    - Leap of Faith, Ocean Beach, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 15, Folder 396)
    - Listen Up, 18th Street near Castro, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 15, Folder 397)
    - Man and Magazine, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 15, Folder 398)
    - Man in the Knitted Beret, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 15, Folder 399)
    - The Man and the Medium, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 15, Folder 400)
    - A Match, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 15, Folder 401)
    - The Message, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 15, Folder 402)
    - A Metered Gaze, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 15, Folder 403)
    - Mirror Image, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1997 June 15 (Box 15, Folder 404)
    - The Mod Hatter, Alameda Flea Market, Alameda, California, 2009 June 7 (Box 15, Folder 405)
    - Music in the Wind, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 15, Folder 406)
    - My Shoppe, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 15, Folder 407)
    - News Stand, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 16, Folder 408)
    - Nothing Special, Castro Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 16, Folder 409)
    - Ocean Beach, San Francisco, California, 2004 February 14; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 16, Folder 410-411)
    - Of Interest, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 16, Folder 412-413)
    - On the Bench, Market and Castro Streets, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 16, Folder 414)
    - Paich, Slobodan Dan; San Francisco, California, 2006 September 1 (Box 16, Folder 415)
    - Painted Lady, Halloween, Castro, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 16, Folder 416)
    - Painties, Alameda Flea Market, Alameda, California, 2009 June 7 (Box 16, Folder 417)
    - Partners, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 16, Folder 418)
    - Patron, Duarte's Tavern, Pescadero, California, circa 1981 (Box 16, Folder 419)
    - Patty Cake, undated; 3 black and white photographic prints (Box 16, Folder 420-422)
    - Pensive Lady, Silverberg Wedding, Petaluma, California, 1998 August 16 (Box 16, Folder 423)
    - Playing Doctor, Duboce Park, San Francisco, California, 1985 July 26 (Box 16, Folder 424)
    - Prayer and Reflection, Alameda Flea Market, Alameda, California, 2009 June 7 (Box 16, Folder 425)
    - The Princess and the Pot, Alameda Flea Market, Alameda, California, 2009 June 7 (Box 16, Folder 426)
    - The Pumpkin Lady, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 16, Folder 427-428)
    - Raggedy Anthem, Alameda Flea Market, Alameda, California, 2009 June 7 (Box 16, Folder 429)
    - Reaching Out, Pescadero, California, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 430)
    - Rejected Model, Union Square, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 16, Folder 431)
    - Remains of the Day, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 16, Folder 432)
    - Renaissance Players, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 16, Folder 433)
    - Resting Virgin, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 2001 April 28 (Box 17, Folder 434)
    - Rider in Repose, San Francisco Muni, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 17, Folder 435)
    - Round Table, Interior Restaurant, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1998 September 23 (Box 17, Folder 436)
    - Salvation, 25 Cents a Foot, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 17, Folder 437)
    - Seat on the Board, A. Ocean Beach, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 17, Folder 438)
    - Serious Men, Castro, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 17, Folder 439)
    - Shades and Peepers, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 17, Folder 440)
    - Shop Window, Halloween, Castro Street, San Francisco, California, 2007 October 30 (Box 17, Folder 441)
    - Sisters (I), Palace of Fine Arts, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 17, Folder 442)
    - Sisters (II), Palace of Fine Arts, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 17, Folder 443)
    - Skateboarders, West Portal, San Francisco, California, 1998 August 6 (Box 17, Folder 444)
    - Skirt, Stockings, and Shoes, San Francisco, California, 2003 June 14 (Box 17, Folder 445)
    - Smoking on the Sunny Side, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 17, Folder 446)
    - Somatomo, Yasuo, Market Street near Castro, San Francisco, California, 1998 September 23 (Box 17, Folder 447)
    - Store Window, Night, San Francisco, California, 2005 March 29; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 17, Folder 448-449)
    - Store Window, West Portal, San Francisco, California, 1998 August 6 (Box 17, Folder 450)
    - Street Artist, Clayton Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 17, Folder 451)
    - Street Florist, Noe Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 17, Folder 452)
    - Street Musician, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 17, Folder 453)
    - Street Scene, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 17, Folder 454)
    - Sullivan, Miki, A Toast, San Francisco Art Institute, California, 2003 June 14 (Box 17, Folder 455)
    - Sunning on the Quay, Fort Mason, San Francisco, California, 2006 July 22 (Box 17, Folder 456)
    - Swan Lady, Alameda Flea Market, Alameda, California, 2009 June 7 (Box 17, Folder 457)
    - Theater Faces, Market Street, San Francisco, California, undated (Box 17, Folder 458)
    - Them, Oakland, California, undated (Box 18, Folder 459)
    - Toutes les Nuits du Monde, Union Square from 291 Geary Street, San Francisco, California, 2009 March 31 (Box 18, Folder 460)
    - Unconditional Devotion, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 461-462)
    - Vector, Castro, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 19 (Box 18, Folder 463)
    - Visions of Self Reference, Alameda Flea Market, Alameda, California, 2009 June 7 (Box 18, Folder 464)
    - Warning, Butano Canyon, Pescadero, California, undated (Box 18, Folder 465)
    - Wax Museum, San Francisco, California, 1992 December 20 (Box 18, Folder 466)
    - Work Boots at Rest, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 1983 October 20 (Box 18, Folder 467)
    - Young Amazon Warrior, Market Street, San Francisco, California, 2001 April 28 (Box 18, Folder 468)
    - Young Horsewoman, San Francisco, California, undated; 2 black and white photographic prints (Box 18, Folder 469-470)
    - Young Photographer At the Museum, Palace of the Legion of Honor, San Francisco, California, 2004 July 14 (Box 18, Folder 471)
- Scenes from the American West, 1982-2008; Series III; 1; (5 boxes)
  Organized into two subseries: Photographic Prints 8 x 10 inches and Photographic Prints 11 x 14 inches.
  Photographs of sites throughout the American West.
  - Photographic Prints 8 x 10 Inches
    Arranged geographically
    - Arkansas
      - Eureka Springs
        - Integration, Antique Display, The Painted Pony, Eureka Springs, Arkansas, 1993 April 28 (Box 19, Folder 472)
        - Ma Brown's Sanctuary, Route 62, Near Eureka Springs, Arkansas, 1993 April 28 (Box 19, Folder 473)
      - Hot Springs
        - Bronze Statue, Hot Springs, Arkansas, undated (Box 19, Folder 474)
      - Mountain View
        - Pasture Gate, Route 5 South of Mountain View, Arkansas, 1993 April 29 (Box 19, Folder 475)
        - Whitfield, Walter, Mountain View, Arkansas, 1993 April 28 (Box 19, Folder 476)
      - Unisex Outhouse, Rural Arkansas, undated (Box 19, Folder 477)
    - California
      - Eastern Sierra
        - Moonrise, Bishop, California, undated (Box 19, Folder 478)
        - Rural Church, Near Bridgeport, California, Eastern Sierra, undated (Box 19, Folder 479)
      - Joshua Tree Monument
        - Joshua Tree Monument, California, undated (Box 19, Folder 480)
      - Mono Lake
        - Tufa, Mono Lake, California, undated (Box 19, Folder 481)
      - Owens Valley
        - Brush and Clouds, Owens Valley, California, undated (Box 19, Folder 482)
        - Lone Tree, Owens Valley, California, 1993 January 5 (Box 19, Folder 483)
        - Looking West, Owens Valley, California, undated (Box 19, Folder 484)
      - Pescadero
        - Interior, Abandoned Building, Willowside Farm, Stage Road, Pescadero, California, undated (Box 19, Folder 485)
        - Willowside Farm, Stage Road, Pescadero, California, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 486)
          Architectural photograph with a Sabattier effect
      - Sacramento River Delta
        - Bridge, Night, Sacramento River Delta, California, undated (Box 19, Folder 487)
        - Quiet Time, Sacramento River Delta, California, undated (Box 19, Folder 488)
      - San Francisco
        - Undercast, Looking North, Golden Gate, San Francisco, California, 2006 July 13 (Box 19, Folder 489)
    - Colorado
      - Masks, Denver Art Museum, Denver, Colorado, undated (Box 19, Folder 490)
  - Photographic Prints 11 x 14 Inches
    - Arizona
      - Aguila
        - Klimek's Saddle, Aguila, Arizona, 2004 May 8 (Box 20, Folder 491)
      - Ajo
        - Church, Detail, Ajo, Arizona, 2004 May 7 (Box 20, Folder 492)
      - Casa Grande
        - Saguaro Silhouette, Casa Grande, Southern Arizona, 1995 March 17 (Box 20, Folder 493)
        - Saguaro Silhouette, Casa Grande, Arizona, 1995 March 18 (Box 20, Folder 494)
        - Sleeping Serpent, Casa Grande, Arizona, 1995 March 17 (Box 20, Folder 495)
      - Chandler
        - Left Field, Chandler, Arizona, 1995 March 17 (Box 20, Folder 496)
      - San Xavier Indian Reservation
        - Howling Wolf, San Xavier Del Bac, Arizona, 1995 March 18 (Box 20, Folder 497)
        - Mission Arches, San Xavier Del Bac, Arizona, undated (Box 20, Folder 498)
        - San Xavier Del Bac, Detail, Southern Arizona, undated (Box 20, Folder 499)
      - Santa Cruz County
        - Mission San José de Tumacácori, Southern Arizona, undated (Box 20, Folder 500)
      - Tucson
        - Solid Sleep, Tucson, Arizona, undated (Box 20, Folder 501)
      - Wilcox
        - Country Store, Wilcox, Arizona, undated (Box 20, Folder 502)
        - Industrial Site, Wilcox, Arizona, undated (Box 20, Folder 503)
      - Unidentified locations in Southern Arizona
        - Apache Shrine, Southern Arizona, 2004 May 7 (Box 20, Folder 504)
        - Church, Interior, Southern Arizona, undated (Box 20, Folder 505)
        - Yucca Flower Detail, Southern Arizona, undated (Box 20, Folder 506)
        - Image with Image Maker, Southern Arizona, 2004 May 7 (Box 20, Folder 507)
        - Lonesome Yucca, Southern Arizona, 2004 May 7 (Box 20, Folder 508)
        - Rural Church, Southern Arizona, 2004 May 7 (Box 20, Folder 509)
    - Arkansas
      - Eureka Springs
        - Mother and Daughter, Eureka Springs, Arkansas, 1993 April 27 (Box 20, Folder 510)
      - St. Joe
        - Abandoned Building, St. Joe, Arkansas, 1993 April 28 (Box 20, Folder 511)
      - Unidentified locations in Arkansas
        - Old Stone Barber Shop, Route 62, Rural Arkansas, 1993 April 28 (Box 20, Folder 512)
        - Rural Barn at Dawn, near Fort Smith, Arkansas, 1993 April 28 (Box 20, Folder 513)
    - California
      - Altamont Pass
        - Early A.M. (I), Altamont Pass, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 514)
        - Early A.M. (II), Altamont Pass, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 515)
      - Arcata
        - Father and Son, Arcata Plaza, Arcata, California, 2005 August 15 (Box 21, Folder 516)
        - Peeling Paint, Broken Windows, Roadside, Arcata, California, 2005 August 14 (Box 21, Folder 517)
        - Summer Light, Arcata Bottoms, Arcata, California, 2005 August 14 (Box 21, Folder 518)
      - Bodie
        - Church Interior, Bodie, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 519)
        - Door, Detail, Bodie, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 520)
        - Door and Chair, Bodie, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 521)
        - Doorway, Detail, Bodie, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 522)
        - Homage to John Sexton, Bodie, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 523)
        - Interior, Detail, Bodie, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 524)
        - Machinery Parts, Detail, Bodie, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 525)
        - Mining Machinery (I), Detail, Bodie, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 526)
        - Mining Machinery (II), Detail, Bodie, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 527)
        - Old Automobile, Detail, Bodie, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 528)
        - Old Springs, Bodie, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 529)
        - Old Truck, Bodie, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 530)
        - Ranger's Residence, Bodie, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 531)
        - Window, Detail, Bodie, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 532)
      - Columbia
        - Church, Columbia, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 533)
      - Colusa County
        - Abandoned Barn, near Route 5, Colusa County, Northern California, 2003 April 13 (Box 21, Folder 534)
      - Death Valley
        - Sand Dunes, Stove Pipe Wells, Death Valley, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 535)
      - Dunnigan
        - Bull and Kathy, Route 5, Dunnigan, California, 2003 April 6 (Box 21, Folder 536)
      - Healdsburg
        - Heavenly Clouds, Healdsburg Cemetery, Healdsburg, California, 1997 November 4 (Box 21, Folder 537)
      - Jolon
        - Covered Walk-Way, Mission San Antonio de Padua, California, undated (Box 21, Folder 538)
        - Mission San Antonio de Padua, Detail, California, 1993 May 14 (Box 21, Folder 539)
      - Los Angeles
        - Curran's Kitchen, Los Angeles, California, 2004 May 2 (Box 22, Folder 540)
      - Mono Lake
        - Abandoned Ranch, Mono Lake, California, undated (Box 22, Folder 541)
        - South Tufa, Mono Lake, California, 1996 June7 (Box 22, Folder 542)
        - Tufa, Mono Lake, California, undated (Box 22, Folder 543)
      - Owens Valley
        - Aspens in Autumn, Owens Valley, California, undated (Box 22, Folder 544)
        - Masonic Grave Marker, Owens Valley, California, undated (Box 22, Folder 545)
      - Panamint Valley
        - Panamint Dry Lake on a Wet Day, Panamint Valley, California, undated (Box 22, Folder 546)
        - Sun Bleached Branch, Detail, Panamint Valley, California, undated (Box 22, Folder 547)
        - Sun Bleached Tumbleweed, Panamint Valley, California, undated (Box 22, Folder 548)
      - Pescadero
        - Equus, Willowside Farm, Pescadero, California, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 549)
        - Window, Detail, Abandoned Farm Building, Willowside Farm, Pescadero, California, undated (Box 22, Folder 550)
      - Randsburg
        - Pipes, Detail, Randsburg, California, undated (Box 22, Folder 551)
      - San Francisco
        - Art and Shadow, Palace of the Legion of Honor, San Francisco, California, 2006 July 13 (Box 22, Folder 552)
        - Cultural Convergence, Palace of the Legion of Honor, San Francisco, California, 2004 July 14 (Box 22, Folder 553)